<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>PainCompiler</title>
    <link>http://blog.paincompiler.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on PainCompiler</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2016 21:48:59 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://blog.paincompiler.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>College Graduated Like A Drop Out</title>
      <link>http://blog.paincompiler.com/post/College-Graduated-Like-A-Drop-Uut/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2016 21:48:59 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.paincompiler.com/post/College-Graduated-Like-A-Drop-Uut/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;So, it&amp;rsquo;s the college graduation session in China.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Techniac</title>
      <link>http://blog.paincompiler.com/post/Techniac/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Oct 2015 00:57:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.paincompiler.com/post/Techniac/</guid>
      <description>&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-lisp&#34;&gt;`(defun techniac-generate (fn &amp;amp;rest key-args)
...
)
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;`
It&amp;rsquo;s hard to re-pick the &lt;em&gt;pen&lt;/em&gt; but somehow, one year later, I come back to here.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What The Geek</title>
      <link>http://blog.paincompiler.com/post/What-The-Geek/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2014 17:54:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.paincompiler.com/post/What-The-Geek/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Everybody nowdays is yelling like &lt;em&gt;the world gone krazy&lt;/em&gt;. But actually, man is the krazy one and the whole thing went wrong with da madness of ourselves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apart from the main world stream, we can see events people make, whatever big or negligible, can always change the direction of the main stream, and GEEKs should be one of those people who taka a role in this era.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But it&amp;rsquo;s not about geek at first I wanna talk, it&amp;rsquo;s GEEKLESS and ANTI-GEEK.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;geekless-anti-geek&#34;&gt;GEEKLESS&amp;amp;ANTI-GEEK&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Defining a word is kinda usual thing while we are reaching the discuss level of it, but I will give a few words to describe what I think of Geek but to define it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People always got mad at what they don&amp;rsquo;t know about, and, the same time, puff at what they know a little about, which I consider it worse than the other one. And up to the popular concept, it&amp;rsquo;s more easy for everybody to talking sh1t like &amp;lsquo;anybody can be anything&amp;rsquo; sh1t.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For &amp;lsquo;geek&amp;rsquo;, which is not a brand new thing, the past five years has been a hit word especially in technology field.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Start It From Scratch</title>
      <link>http://blog.paincompiler.com/post/Start-it-from-scratch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2014 01:26:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.paincompiler.com/post/Start-it-from-scratch/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;You may notice that I say &amp;lsquo;it&amp;rsquo; in the title, and what I&amp;rsquo;m about to tell you is, YES, it&amp;rsquo;s not about &amp;lsquo;IT&amp;rsquo;. Just it, which refers to HipHop.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No doubt I&amp;rsquo;m a big fan of HipHop and I do it everyday, which gives me da confidence to say YES I AM HIPHOP.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve been busy developing these days and the coming days, when I release my brain I just don&amp;rsquo;t wanna talk too much about programming. So I wanna talk about my HipHop life. I don&amp;rsquo;t wanna anyone judge me you know what I mean. Piz&amp;amp;Luv.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;when-and-how&#34;&gt;When and How&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are somebody know me somethin&amp;rsquo;, you may know dat I can do a lot about what i&amp;rsquo;m fond of, I mean lots kinds areas of HipHop. I do poplock dance, old-skool HipHop dance, making beats, writtin&amp;rsquo; and a little rap.I can dance some really, but in fact, I start doing HipHop from rap.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s hard to recall the my first &amp;lsquo;waking&amp;rsquo; of my HipHop soul (lol), but the biggest thang dat made me think about being HipHop is da first time I heard of da song &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Big Poppa&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; by &lt;strong&gt;The Notorious B.I.G&lt;/strong&gt; (I miss you so much) when I was 14 (summer of 2007).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then da story just be what it is supposed to be typically. I started to do da research of HipHop. From Biggie to my man Nas then WuTang Clan, from east to da west coast and from 90&amp;rsquo;s back to 80&amp;rsquo;s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At da first two years I&amp;rsquo;ve collect lots of CDs and I start to write some lyrics when I was in my third year of middle skool (but I was still in golden age and old-skool lol). And at the same time I start to know the dance, which was influenced by da K-POP culture flooding the entertainment of China. I start it from doing some break dance tricks then I got my poppin&amp;rsquo; dance. I practice it really hard and got some respect at the local street dance circle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My dad is a Classic music and HiFi device maniac, so I played violin when I was only 3 and a half year old, which gives me da great sense and accomplishment of music and art (don&amp;rsquo;t judge me! lol).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All of these make me do it dis far.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;keep-on-dancing&#34;&gt;Keep On Dancing&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now days we always talk about &amp;ldquo;Go back to da street&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Keep it real&amp;rdquo;. Well I&amp;rsquo;m nuthin&amp;rsquo; against them and I consider them as some fantastic phenomenon and spirits of HipHop.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In fact I know there&amp;rsquo;re lots of unhealthy and over commercial stuff and some of them has been making nasty thing about our beloved culture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But, hey dude, calm down! Just don&amp;rsquo;t hate things 4 bunches hates around you. If it&amp;rsquo;s not the commercial stuff, we people out of the origin (America) know sh1t about HipHop, rap and dance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I started my dance from the K-POP dance, which takes lots of elements from da HipHop dance. I just couldn&amp;rsquo;t stop watching H.O.T and HyunJun videos when I was 14. Thy are dope artist dancing well -
right, they are artist but not dancer (may little sissy about da conception).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I start to know more about the real HipHop dance when I saw da Electric Boogaloo dropped down in KOD vol.5, doing da dope poppin&amp;rsquo; dance first while I was just waving in my poppin&amp;rsquo; lol. It wake my soul up and take my first step in HipHop dance(not HipHop, I already listened to real rap music as you know).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With my K-POP foundation, I joined da street dance studio in my high skool, which called &lt;em&gt;The One Dance Crew&lt;/em&gt; (kinda cool aight?). The leader of my crew is a popper and he&amp;rsquo;s just ok at dancing (of course better than I used to be), but mean with people. He just loved battling wit me the whole afternoon, results in dat I was exhausted and He just felt good (cuz He&amp;rsquo;s better than me). One year later, as you can imagine, I was gettin&amp;rsquo; better and better wit a amazing speed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I was in da third grade in high skool, I had won lots of battles and games. Then me and my friends, who just love da culture comes from street ,founded da &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ZigZag Street Culture Studio&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; in my hometown. We did graffiti, producing, street dance and rap. I taught poppin&amp;rsquo; and lockin&amp;rsquo; there and made lots of friends. These days is one of my best memory in my life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nuthin&amp;rsquo; lasts 4ever, me and my friends who are the leaders of da studio broke up. They wanna make money by teaching so called &amp;ldquo;losing weight HipHop dance&amp;rdquo;, which is just awful to me. So I left actually, but I still keep on dancing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I founded da first street dance studio in my acadamy when I was in my first year in collage, named &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DancersDelight Crew&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;. People come people go, we now have 40 people, some are jazz dancer, some are poppers, some are bboy and some are lockers.We are just like a big family, when we hang together, I just recall da saying dat &amp;ldquo;HipHop makes us brothers and sisters together&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;i-m-rappin-2-da-beats&#34;&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m Rappin&amp;rsquo; 2 Da Beats&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Now wat ya hear is not a test I&amp;rsquo;m rappin&amp;rsquo; 2 da beats~&amp;rdquo;, I barely talks about my lyrics cuz I&amp;rsquo;m not good at rappin&amp;rsquo; at all. I know I have been addicted in rap music about 8 years long (well, might not as long as you b1tches lol, mean not offense), and I do research da skill about rap and mc-ing&amp;rsquo;, but I just have not built up my confidence to rap. I just need one mic and one step up to stand on stage. I&amp;rsquo;m going 2 do dat recently! Yeah man, dope rapper NastyLeoc. lol~&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;PS.I will put some of my lyrics upon there sooner or later&amp;hellip;kinda weird but I&amp;rsquo;m gonna do dat&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;HipHop saved my life&amp;rdquo;, I&amp;rsquo;m just another sample to prove dis. I used to love hangin&amp;rsquo; out wit girls when I&amp;rsquo;m just 13 and 14, even did some nasty thang (burning a huge ad. board, stealing money from my parents&amp;hellip;). Rapper may say something krazy and violent I know but I&amp;rsquo;ve paid more attention to da positive section. I won&amp;rsquo;t list da lyrics from dis great rapper cuz you may know a lot more than me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Only one thing to say: &amp;ldquo; I&amp;rsquo;m HipHop and it made me who I am &amp;ldquo;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;start-it-from-scratch&#34;&gt;Start It From Scratch&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m a electronic maniac, so it&amp;rsquo;s kinda nature 4 me 2 making music with computer and midi devices.I started it from making dancing beats by &lt;strong&gt;Fruity Loop&lt;/strong&gt; , which just met my need and is easy to use.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve made lots of beats demo but never publish or push them to the public. Just like I like rapping to it but never release a record.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know I gotta do it right now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There&amp;rsquo;s a long way to go but time is limited for a person.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Love is love but we need to do it right now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I started it from scratch, and never stop.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://blog.paincompiler.com/post/Untitled/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.paincompiler.com/post/Untitled/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>